<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<List>
  <Life>
    <quote name="sucess">
      <advice>Coming together is a beginning; keeping together is progress; working together is success. Henry Ford</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="sucess">
      <advice>Success is not final, failure is not fatal: it is the courage to continue that counts. Winston Churchill
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="sucess">
      <advice>The price of success is hard work, dedication to the job at hand, and the determination that whether we win or lose, we have applied the best of ourselves to the task at hand. Vince Lombardi</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="sucess">
      <advice>Always be yourself, express yourself, have faith in yourself, do not go out and look for a successful personality and duplicate it.Bruce Lee
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="sucess">
      <advice>Try not to become a man of success, but rather try to become a man of value.Albert Einstein</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="sucess">
      <advice>Success is nothing more than a few simple disciplines, practiced every day.Jim Rohn</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="sucess">
      <advice>
        Success is a lousy teacher. It seduces smart people into thinking they can't lose.Bill Gates
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="sucess">
      <advice>Happiness lies in the joy of achievement and the thrill of creative effort.
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="sucess">
      <advice>No man succeeds without a good woman behind him. Wife or mother, if it is both, he is twice </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="sucess">
      <advice>Strive not to be a success, but rather to be of value. Albert Einstein
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="family">
      <advice>You don't choose your family. They are God's gift to you, as you are to them. Desmond Tutu</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="family">
      <advice>The other night I ate at a real nice family restaurant. Every table had an argument going. George Carlin
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="family">
      <advice>Sister is probably the most competitive relationship within the family, but once the sisters are grown, it becomes the strongest relationship. Margaret Mead</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="family">
      <advice>I'll never stop dreaming that one day we can be a real family, together, all of us laughing and talking, loving and understanding, not looking at the past but only to the future. LaToya Jackson
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="family">
      <advice>Family is the most important thing in the world. Princess Diana
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="family">
      <advice>To us, family means putting your arms around each other and being there. Barbara Bush
      </advice>
    </quote>
      <quote name="family">
      <advice>The only rock I know that stays steady, the only institution I know that works, is the family.</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="family">
      <advice>A happy family is but an earlier heaven. George Bernard Shaw</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="family">
      <advice>There's nothing I value more than the closeness of friends and family, a smile as I pass someone on the street. Willie Stargell</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="family">
      <advice>Children are the keys of paradise. Eric Hoffer</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="music">
      <advice>If music be the food of love, play on. William Shakespeare
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="music">
      <advice>Where words fail, music speaks. Hans Christian Andersen
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="music">
      <advice>One good thing about music, when it hits you, you feel no pain.
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="music">
      <advice>Beautiful music is the art of the prophets that can calm the agitations of the soul; it is one of the most magnificent and delightful presents God has given us. Martin Luther   
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="music">
      <advice>Music can change the world because it can change people. Bono
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="music">
      <advice>Without music, life would be a mistake. Friedrich Nietzsche
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="music">
      <advice>Music is a higher revelation than all wisdom and philosophy. Ludwig van Beethoven</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="music">
      <advice>Music should strike fire from the heart of man, and bring tears from the eyes of woman. Ludwig van Beethoven</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="music">
      <advice>Music is God's gift to man, the only art of Heaven given to earth, the only art of earth we take to Heaven. Walter Savage Landor</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="music">
      <advice>Tones sound, and roar and storm about me until I have set them down in notes. Ludwig van Beethoven</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="education">
      <advice>The function of education is to teach one to think intensively and to think critically. Intelligence plus character - that is the goal of true education. Martin Luther King, Jr.
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="education">
      <advice>The only person who is educated is the one who has learned how to learn and change. Carl Rogers
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="education">
      <advice>Education is the key to unlock the golden door of freedom. George Washington Carver</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="education">
      <advice>Education is the best friend. An educated person is respected everywhere. Education beats the beauty and the youth. Chanakya</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="education">
      <advice>A library is the delivery room for the birth of ideas, a place where history comes to life. Norman Cousins</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="education">
      <advice>To educate a man in mind and not in morals is to educate a menace to society. Theodore Roosevelt</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="education">
      <advice>The only fence against the world is a thorough knowledge of it. John Locke</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="education">
      <advice>Education is the movement from darkness to light. Allan Bloom</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="education">
      <advice>It is a miracle that curiosity survives formal education. Albert Einstein</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="education">
      <advice>Give a man a fish and you feed him for a day; teach a man to fish and you feed him for a lifetime. Maimonides</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="birthday">
      <advice>Let us never know what old age is. Let us know the happiness time brings, not count the years. Ausonius
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="birthday">
      <advice>Cakes are special. Every birthday, every celebration ends with something sweet, a cake, and people remember. It's all about the memories. Buddy Valastro
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="birthday">
      <advice>Let us never know what old age is. Let us know the happiness time brings, not count the years. Ausonius</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="birthday">
      <advice>Every year on your birthday, you get a chance to start new. Sammy Hagar</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="birthday">
      <advice>A birthday is just another day where you go to work and people give you love. Age is just a state of mind, and you are as old as you think you are. You have to count your blessings and be happy. Abhishek Bachchan</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="birthday">
      <advice>God gave us the gift of life; it is up to us to give ourselves the gift of living well. Voltaire</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="birthday">
      <advice>You take away all the other luxuries in life, and if you can make someone smile and laugh, you have given the most special gift: happiness. Brad Garrett</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="birthday">
      <advice>It takes a long time to become young. Pablo Picasso</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="birthday">
      <advice>The great thing about getting older is that you don't lose all the other ages you've been. Madeleine L'Engle</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="birthday">
      <advice>I'm a summer baby, so I usually have my birthday as a good summer memory. Sloane Crosley</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="friendship">
      <advice>One of the most beautiful qualities of true friendship is to understand and to be understood. Lucius Annaeus Seneca
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="friendship">
      <advice>Friendship is always a sweet responsibility, never an opportunity. Khalil Gibran
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="friendship">
      <advice>A real friend is one who walks in when the rest of the world walks out. Walter Winchell</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="friendship">
      <advice>Friends are the siblings God never gave us. Mencius</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="friendship">
      <advice>Friends show their love in times of trouble, not in happiness. Euripides</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="friendship">
      <advice>A true friend freely, advises justly, assists readily, adventures boldly, takes all patiently, defends courageously, and continues a friend unchangeably. William Penn</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="friendship">
      <advice>Sometimes being a friend means mastering the art of timing. There is a time for silence. A time to let go and allow people to hurl themselves into their own destiny. And a time to prepare to pick up the pieces when it's all over. Octavia Butler</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="friendship">
      <advice>Love is blind; friendship closes its eyes. Friedrich Nietzsche</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="friendship">
      <advice>Friends show their love in times of trouble, not in happiness. Euripides</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="friendship">
      <advice>Love is the only force capable of transforming an enemy into friend. Martin Luther King, Jr</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="nature">
      <advice>Just living is not enough... one must have sunshine, freedom, and a little flower. Hans Christian Andersen
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="nature">
      <advice>On earth there is no heaven, but there are pieces of it. Jules Renard
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="nature">
      <advice>Nature holds the key to our aesthetic, intellectual, cognitive and even spiritual satisfaction. E. O. Wilson</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="nature">
      <advice>Autumn is a second spring when every leaf is a flower. Albert Camus</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="nature">
      <advice>Every flower is a soul blossoming in nature. Gerard De Nerval</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="nature">
      <advice>The sea, once it casts its spell, holds one in its net of wonder forever. Jacques Yves Cousteau</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="nature">
      <advice>There are always flowers for those who want to see them. Henri Matisse</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="nature">
      <advice>Green is the prime color of the world, and that from which its loveliness arises. Pedro Calderon de la Barca</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="nature">
      <advice>Earth and sky, woods and fields, lakes and rivers, the mountain and the sea, are excellent schoolmasters, and teach some of us more than we can ever learn from books. John Lubbock</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="nature">
      <advice>In the depth of winter I finally learned that there was in me an invincible summer. Albert Camus</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="pollution">
      <advice>Sooner or later, we will have to recognise that the Earth has rights, too, to live without pollution. What mankind must know is that human beings cannot live without Mother Earth, but the planet can live without humans. Evo Morales
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="pollution">
      <advice>Environmental pollution is an incurable disease. It can only be prevented. Barry Commoner
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="pollution">
      <advice>The problem is that everywhere the gas drilling industry goes, a trail of water contamination, air pollution, health concerns and betrayal of basic American civic and community values follows. Josh Fox</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="pollution">
      <advice>I don't want to wait 20 or 50 years for something to be done about petrochemical pollution. Jack Herer</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="pollution">
      <advice>Australia is the only island continent on the planet, which means that changes caused by planet-warming pollution - warmer seas, which can drive stronger storms, and more acidic oceans, which wreak havoc on the food chain - are even more deadly here. Jeff Goodell</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="pollution">
      <advice>There's so much pollution in the air now that if it weren't for our lungs there'd be no place to put it all. Robert Orben</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="pollution">
      <advice>Like a tracer running through the veins of the city, networks of air quality sensors attached to bikes can help measure an individual's exposure to pollution and draw a dynamic map of the urban air on a human scale, as in the case of the Copenhagen Wheel developed by new startup Superpedestrian. Carlo Ratti</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="pollution">
      <advice>Because cap and trade is enforced through the selling and trading of permits, it actually perpetuates the pollution it is supposed to eliminate. James Hansen</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="pollution">
      <advice>The environment will continue to deteriorate until pollution practices are abandoned. B. F. Skinner</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="pollution">
      <advice>The Chinese have figured out that they have a giant environmental problem. Folks in Beijing, some days, literally can't breathe. Over a million Chinese die prematurely every year because of air pollution. Joe Biden</advice>
    </quote>
  </Life>
  <psy>
    <quote name="love">
      <advice>Love isn't something you find. Love is something that finds you. Loretta Young</advice>
    </quote>
  <quote name="love">
      <advice>Love is when the other person's happiness is more important than your own. H. Jackson Brown, Jr.</advice>
    </quote>
  <quote name="love">
      <advice>Immature love says: 'I love you because I need you.' Mature love says 'I need you because I love you.' Erich Fromm</advice>
    </quote>
<quote name="love">
      <advice>You can't blame gravity for falling in love. Albert Einstein
</advice>
    </quote>
  <quote name="love">
      <advice>Sometimes the heart sees what is invisible to the eye. H. Jackson Brown, Jr.
</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="love">
      <advice>Let us always meet each other with smile, for the smile is the beginning of love. Mother Teresa
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="love">
      <advice>Let us always meet each other with smile, for the smile is the beginning of love. Mother Teresa
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="love">
      <advice>The best thing to hold onto in life is each other. Audrey Hepburn
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="love">
      <advice>A flower cannot blossom without sunshine, and man cannot live without love. Max Muller
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="love">
      <advice>Love is composed of a single soul inhabiting two bodies. Aristotle
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="motivation">
      <advice>In order to succeed, we must first believe that we can. Nikos Kazantzakis
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="motivation">
      <advice>Accept the challenges so that you can feel the exhilaration of victory. George S. Patton
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="motivation">
      <advice>What you do today can improve all your tomorrows. Ralph Marston
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="motivation">
      <advice>A creative man is motivated by the desire to achieve, not by the desire to beat others. Ayn Rand
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="motivation">
      <advice>Our greatest weakness lies in giving up. The most certain way to succeed is always to try just one more time. Thomas A. Edison
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="motivation">
      <advice>You can't cross the sea merely by standing and staring at the water. Rabindranath Tagore
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="motivation">
      <advice>Start where you are. Use what you have. Do what you can. Arthur Ashe</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="motivation">
      <advice>Knowing is not enough; we must apply. Willing is not enough; we must do. Johann Wolfgang von Goethe</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="motivation">
      <advice>Never give up, for that is just the place and time that the tide will turn. Harriet Beecher Stowe
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="motivation">
      <advice>Ever tried. Ever failed. No matter. Try Again. Fail again. Fail better. Samuel Beckett
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="sad">
      <advice>The word 'happiness' would lose its meaning if it were not balanced by sadness. Carl Jung
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="sad">
      <advice>Heavy hearts, like heavy clouds in the sky, are best relieved by the letting of a little water. Christopher Morley
      </advice>
    </quote>
     <quote name="sad">
      <advice>Every human walks around with a certain kind of sadness. They may not wear it on their sleeves, but it's there if you look deep. Taraji P. Henson
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="sad">
      <advice>I've cried, and you'd think I'd be better for it, but the sadness just sleeps, and it stays in my spine the rest of my life. Conor Oberst</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="sad">
      <advice>You left and I cried tears of blood. My sorrow grows. Its not just that You left. But when You left my eyes went with You. Now, how will I cry? Rumi
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="sad">
      <advice>Sorrows are like thunderclouds, in the distance they look black, over our heads scarcely gray. Jean Paul</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="sad">
      <advice>Depression is the inability to construct a future. Rollo May
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="sad">
      <advice>Worry never robs tomorrow of its sorrow, it only saps today of its joy. Leo Buscaglia
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="sad">
      <advice>Those who don't know how to weep with their whole heart, don't know how to laugh either. Golda Meir</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="sad">
      <advice>They say it's better to bury your sadness in a graveyard or garden that waits for the spring to wake from its sleep and burst into green. Conor Oberst</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="wisdom">
      <advice>Do not go where the path may lead, go instead where there is no path and leave a trail. Ralph Waldo Emerson
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="wisdom">
      <advice>The journey of a thousand miles begins with one step. Lao Tzu
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="wisdom">
      <advice>The only true wisdom is in knowing you know nothing. Socrates
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="wisdom">
      <advice>It takes a great man to give sound advice tactfully, but a greater to accept it graciously. Logan Pearsall Smith
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="wisdom">
      <advice>Whatever you do in life, surround yourself with smart people who'll argue with you. John Wooden</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="wisdom">
      <advice>A man must be big enough to admit his mistakes, smart enough to profit from them, and strong enough to correct them. John C. Maxwell</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="wisdom">
      <advice>A good head and a good heart are always a formidable combination. Nelson Mandela</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="wisdom">
      <advice>The pessimist complains about the wind; the optimist expects it to change; the realist adjusts the sails. William Arthur Ward
      </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="wisdom">
      <advice>Be as you wish to seem. Socrates</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="wisdom">
      <advice>Reality is merely an illusion, albeit a very persistent one. Albert Einstein</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="smile">
      <advice>A gentle word, a kind look, a good-natured smile can work wonders and accomplish miracles. William Hazlitt</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="smile">
      <advice>Don't cry because it's over. Smile because it happened. Dr. Seuss</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="smile">
      <advice>A smile is happiness you'll find right under your nose. Tom Wilson</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="smile">
      <advice>We shall never know all the good that a simple smile can do. Mother Teresa</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="smile">
      <advice>A smile is a curve that sets everything straight. Phyllis Diller </advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="smile">
      <advice>Smile, it's free therapy. Douglas Horton</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="smile">
      <advice>Always keep your smile. That's how I explain my long life. Jeanne Calment</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="smile">
      <advice>A kind heart is a fountain of gladness, making everything in its vicinity freshen into smiles. Washington Irving</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="smile">
      <advice>Look back, and smile on perils past. Walter Scott</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="smile">
      <advice>I think that anybody that smiles automatically looks better. Diane Lane</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="happiness">
      <advice>It is not how much we have, but how much we enjoy, that makes happiness. Charles Spurgeon</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="happiness">
      <advice>True happiness is... to enjoy the present, without anxious dependence upon the future. Lucius Annaeus Seneca</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="happiness">
      <advice>Be happy with what you have and are, be generous with both, and you won't have to hunt for happiness. William E. Gladstone</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="happiness">
      <advice>The moments of happiness we enjoy take us by surprise. It is not that we seize them, but that they seize us. Ashley Montagu</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="happiness">
      <advice>Happiness is not a matter of intensity but of balance, order, rhythm and harmony. Thomas Merton</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="happiness">
      <advice>Most folks are as happy as they make up their minds to be. Abraham Lincoln</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="happiness">
      <advice>True happiness comes from the joy of deeds well done, the zest of creating things new. Antoine de Saint-Exupery</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="happiness">
      <advice>t is neither wealth nor splendor; but tranquility and occupation which give you happiness. Thomas Jefferson</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="happiness">
      <advice>When ambition ends, happiness begins. Thomas Merton</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="happiness">
      <advice>Happiness: an agreeable sensation arising from contemplating the misery of another. Ambrose Bierce</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="inspiration">
      <advice>Perfection is not attainable, but if we chase perfection we can catch excellence. Vince Lombardi</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="inspiration">
      <advice>Try to be a rainbow in someone's cloud. Maya Angelou</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="inspiration">
      <advice>If I have seen further than others, it is by standing upon the shoulders of giants. Isaac Newton</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="inspiration">
      <advice>We must let go of the life we have planned, so as to accept the one that is waiting for us. Joseph Campbell</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="inspiration">
      <advice>Let us sacrifice our today so that our children can have a better tomorrow. A. P. J. Abdul Kalam</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="inspiration">
      <advice>It is during our darkest moments that we must focus to see the light. Aristotle Onassis</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="inspiration">
      <advice>Put your heart, mind, and soul into even your smallest acts. This is the secret of success. Swami Sivananda</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="inspiration">
      <advice>No act of kindness, no matter how small, is ever wasted. Aesop</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="inspiration">
      <advice>A hero is someone who has given his or her life to something bigger than oneself. Joseph Campbell</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="inspiration">
      <advice>Health is the greatest gift, contentment the greatest wealth, faithfulness the best relationship. Buddha</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="loneliness">
      <advice>Loneliness is my least favorite thing about life. The thing that I'm most worried about is just being alone without anybody to care for or someone who will care for me. Anne Hathaway</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="loneliness">
      <advice>Loneliness adds beauty to life. It puts a special burn on sunsets and makes night air smell better. Henry Rollins</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="loneliness">
      <advice>Loneliness and the feeling of being unwanted is the most terrible poverty. Mother Teresa</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="loneliness">
      <advice>Negative emotions like loneliness, envy, and guilt have an important role to play in a happy life; they're big, flashing signs that something needs to change. Gretchen Rubin</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="loneliness">
      <advice>Too much self-centered attitude, you see, brings, you see, isolation. Result: loneliness, fear, anger. The extreme self-centered attitude is the source of suffering. Dalai Lama</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="loneliness">
      <advice>The essence of Richard Nixon is loneliness. Henry A. Kissinger</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="loneliness">
      <advice>Loneliness is never more cruel than when it is felt in close propinquity with someone who has ceased to communicate. Germaine Greer</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="loneliness">
      <advice>Leadership is the other side of the coin of loneliness, and he who is a leader must always act alone. And acting alone, accept everything alone. Ferdinand Marcos</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="loneliness">
      <advice>There's a difference between solitude and loneliness. Maggie Smith</advice>
    </quote>
    <quote name="loneliness">
      <advice>My inspiration are the woman, friendship, and loneliness. Enrique Iglesias</advice>
    </quote>
  </psy>
</List>